Tufts Daily Records UA176
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negatives, 1905 -- 2004; 1980 -- 2004; UA176.002; 5.0 Linear Feet
  - Features and Arts, Fall and Spring, 2000 -- 2003; UA176.002.017.00002
    - Audio Project: The Mark at Hotung, 2003; UA176.002.017.00002.00099 (Box 17)
    - Student using wireless internet in CC, Prof. Berry; Joey Driver, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.017.00002.00100 (Box 17)
    - Chinatown, 2003; UA176.002.017.00002.00101; Churella, Andrew (Box 17)
    - Ozomatti, 2003; UA176.002.017.00002.00102 (Box 17)
    - Houston Calls; Angie Heimann; Ozomatti, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.017.00002.00103 (Box 17)
    - Aidekman Art Show, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.017.00002.00104; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 17)
    - Cancer Survivor Performance, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.017.00002.00105; Pesavento, Mark (Box 17)
    - Cafe Algiers (Restaurant Review); Jonathan Wilson reading from his new book @bookstore, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.017.00002.00106; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 17)
    - Another Light on the Hill; Black Students at Tufts Exhibit, 2003; UA176.002.017.00002.00107; DeBoer, Jenny (Box 17)
    - Little Shop of Horrors dress rehearsals, 2003; UA176.002.017.00002.00108; DeBoer, Jenny (Box 17)
    - In the Blood Play Rehearsal, 2003; UA176.002.017.00002.00109; Adams (Box 17)
  - News, Fall and Spring, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001
    date approximate
    - Brian Cathcart; Commencement, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00001; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Dibaggs, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00002; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Sheila Bayne, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00003; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 18)
    - The Women's Center, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00004; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 18)
    - De Baggs Speaker, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00005; Yang, Mary (Box 18)
    - Rach Panel, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00006; Marsidi, Jen (Box 18)
    - Bookstore, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00007; Takahashi, Akiko (Box 18)
    - TUTV, 2000; UA176.002.018.00001.00008; Takahashi, Akiko (Box 18)
    - Astro Text, 2000; UA176.002.018.00001.00009; Akiko (Box 18)
    - Shoe Pile, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00010; Burns, Soren (Box 18)
    - Organic Tampons, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00011; Burns, Soren (Box 18)
    - Ex-College Picture, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00012; Burns, Soren (Box 18)
    - Tikip House; Committee, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00013; Dwyer, Erin (Box 18)
    - Residential Life #29-32; M. Rivera (Senator) #1-5, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00014; Scallon, Amy (Box 18)
    - President's Forum, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00015; Marie (Box 18)
    - Light on the Hill, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00016; Marie (Box 18)
    - Light on the Hill, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00017; Marie (Box 18)
    - Police Shots, 2000; UA176.002.018.00001.00018; Kempler, Alissa (Box 18)
    - Engineering Project, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00019; Kempler, Alissa (Box 18)
    - Speaker, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00020; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Veronica Carter, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00021; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Study Abroad, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00022; Stanton, Kit (Box 18)
    - Cultural Festival, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00023; Justin (Box 18)
    - Trustee Lunch, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00024; JSG (Box 18)
    - Trustee Lunch, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00025; JSG (Box 18)
    - Trustee Lunch, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00026; JSG (Box 18)
    - Hazel O'Leary, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00027; JSG (Box 18)
    - Ballots and John Kerry, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00028; Drod (Box 18)
    - Mouse and Career Service, 2000; UA176.002.018.00001.00029; Drod (Box 18)
    - Paveli, 2000; UA176.002.018.00001.00030; Jacob (Box 18)
    - Protest - Announcement of Win, 2000; UA176.002.018.00001.00031; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Protest, 2000; UA176.002.018.00001.00032; Brad; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Protest, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00033 (Box 18)
    - Protest, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00034; Sallin, Chloe (Box 18)
    - EPIIC 2001 (4h 30), 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00035; Sallin, Chloe (Box 18)
    - EPIIC, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00036; Justin (Box 18)
    - EPIIC, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00037; Marie (Box 18)
    - EPIIC, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00038; Brad (Box 18)
    - EPIIC, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00039; Brad (Box 18)
    - EPIIC, 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00040; Carrie (Box 18)
    - Tommy Hilfiger, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00041; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Tommy Hilfiger, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00042; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Eaton, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00001.00043; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
  - Sports, Fall and Spring, 2000 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00002
    includes some 2002
    - Track and Field, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00001; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 18)
      Film form included
    - Track and Field Meet, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00002; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 18)
    - Men's Cross Country, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00003; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 18)
    - Women's Tennis, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00004; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 18)
    - Sports Department Headshots; Fluff; girl scout, blood pressure, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00005; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Field Hockey, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00006; Devon (Box 18)
    - Football, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00007; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Football, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00008; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Unlabelled: Football Headshots, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00009 (Box 18)
    - Men's Soccer - Home, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00010; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Bowdoin Win 3-1, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00011; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Men's Soccer, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00012; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Soccer, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00013; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Women's Varsity Tennis, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00014; Dwyer, Erin (Box 18)
    - Men's and Women's Soccer, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00015; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Women's Soccer, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00016 (Box 18)
    - Women's Soccer, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00017; Brad (Box 18)
    - Women's Soccer Championship, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00018; Trevor (Box 18)
    - Women's Soccer, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00019; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Women's Soccer, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00020; Brad (Box 18)
    - Women's Soccer, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00021; Jenn (Box 18)
    - Unlabelled: Basketball; Track, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00022 (Box 18)
    - Women's Tennis, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00023 (Box 18)
    - Women's Tennis, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00024; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Women's Tennis, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00025; Brad (Box 18)
    - Women's Tennis, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00026; Brad (Box 18)
    - Women's Tennis, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00027; Brad (Box 18)
    - Squash, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00028; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Squash, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00029; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Squash, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00030 (Box 18)
    - Men's Cross Country; Football, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00031; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00032; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00033; Brad (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00034; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00035; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00036; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Hockey; Track, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00037; Brad (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00038; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00039; Brad (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00040; Brad (Box 18)
    - Track, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00041; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00042; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball Headshots, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00043; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00044; Brad; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00045; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball, 2000; UA176.002.018.00002.00046; Brad (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball Headshots, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00047; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00048; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball vs. Brandeis, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00049; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00050; Stitch, B. (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00051; Brad (Box 18)
    - Unlabelled - Indoor Trade, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00052 (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00053; Marie (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00054; Marie (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00055; Marie (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00056; Marie (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00057; Marie (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00058; Marie (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00059; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00060; Brad (Box 18)
    - Men's Volleyball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00061; Brad (Box 18)
    - Unlabelled - Women's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00062 (Box 18)
    - Baseball/Softball, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00063; Jacob (Box 18)
    - Baseball Practice, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00064; Marsidi, Jennifer (Box 18)
      Note included
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00065; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Baseball/Softball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00066; Chloe (Box 18)
    - NESCAC Championship Track Meet, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00067; Turgeon, Euau (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00068; Brad (Box 18)
    - Softball vs. Bowdoin, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00069; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - Baseball vs. Bates, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00070; Jenn (Box 18)
    - Baseball Fun, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00071; Brad (Box 18)
    - Men's Tennis, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00072; Golub, Justin (Box 18)
    - Men's Tennis, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00073; Burns, Soren (Box 18)
    - Softball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00074; Marie (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00075; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00076; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Women's Lacrosse vs. Colby, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00077; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
      Date from binder, Film form included
    - Women's Lacrosse vs. Colby, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00078; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 -- 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00079; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 2002; UA176.002.018.00002.00080; Hayden, Elizabeth (Box 18)
    - Baseball vs. MIT, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00081; Brad (Box 18)
    - Baseball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00082; Brad (Box 18)
    - Baseball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00002.00083; Brad (Box 18)
  - Sports, Spring and Fall, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003
    - Swimming, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00001 (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball vs. Gordon, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00002; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - Volleyball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00003; M., Jennifer (Box 18)
    - Men's Volleyball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00004; Brad (Box 18)
    - Women's Cross Country Meet at Grafton, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00005; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 18)
    - Field Hockey, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00006; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Track and Field, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00007; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 18)
    - Squash vs. Brown, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00008; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - Squash vs. Brown, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00009; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - Squash, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00010; Hendrickson, Christine (Box 18)
      Roster included
    - Squash, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00011; Hendrickson, Christine (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball vs. Connecticut College, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00012; Wittels (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00013; Ferre, Nick (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball vs. Brandeis, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00014; Brad (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00015; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00016; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00017; Trevor (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00018; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Hockey, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00019; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00020; Brad (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00021; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Lynn Cooper, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00022; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Volleyball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00023; M., Jennifer (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00024; Brad (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00025; Trevor (Box 18)
    - Men's Basketball, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00026; Brad (Box 18)
    - Kevin Kelley, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00027; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 18)
    - Unlabelled - Men's Soccer, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00028 (Box 18)
    - Unlabelled, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00029 (Box 18)
    - Unlabelled - Men's Soccer, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00030 (Box 18)
    - Women's Field Hockey vs. Amherst, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00031; Marsidi, Jennifer (Box 18)
    - Men's Soccer, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00032; Sallin, Chloe (Box 18)
    - Men's Cross Country; Roommates, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00033; Gagel, Carrie (Box 18)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Trinity, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00034; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Wesleyan, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00035; Rodriguez, Daniel (Box 18)
    - Men's Soccer, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00036; Sallin, Chloe (Box 18)
    - Softball, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00037; Stitch (Box 18)
    - Women's Field Hockey, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00038; Drod (Box 18)
    - Field Hockey, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00039; M., Jen (Box 18)
    - Field Hockey vs. Middlebury, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00040; M., Jen (Box 18)
    - Women's Ultimate Frisbee Practice, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00041; Sallin, Chloe (Box 18)
    - Football Practice, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00042; M., Jennifer (Box 18)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Middlebury, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00043; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Football Headshots, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00044; M., Jennifer (Box 18)
    - Men's Soccer- Headshots, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00045; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Women's Soccer- Headshots, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00046; Chloe (Box 18)
    - Softball, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00047; Stitch (Box 18)
    - TU Women's Basketball vs. Trinity, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00048; Wittels (Box 18)
    - Unlabelled (Men's Basketball), 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00049 (Box 18)
    - Women's Track, 2002; UA176.002.018.00003.00050; Drod (Box 18)
    - Football, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00051; Drod (Box 18)
    - Football vs. Trinity, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00052; Marsidi, Jennifer (Box 18)
    - Football vs. Trinity, 2001; UA176.002.018.00003.00053; Marsidi, Jennifer (Box 18)
  - Arts and Entertainment, Fall and Spring, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004
    - TASA Show + Essence release party, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00001; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - TASA Show + Essence CD release, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00002; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - 3 Ps/ 4 Short Plays, 2001; UA176.002.018.00004.00003; Chan, Melissa (Box 18)
    - Payton Jazz, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00004; F, Nick (Box 18)
    - Hymnist Spirituals at Godard, 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00005; Carre, Ray (Box 18)
    - Concert Board/ Steve Poole, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00006 (Box 18)
    - Dance Class, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00007 (Box 18)
      Title from sheet, date from binder, film form included
    - Spring Fling 2003, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00008; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Spring Fling, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00009; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Beezlebubs/ Spring Show, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00010; Hayden, Elizabeth (Box 18)
    - Hunger/ Women's Plays, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00011; Taylor, Devon (Box 18)
    - Rooftop Café, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00012; Hayden, Elizabeth (Box 18)
    - Sarabande Show, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00013; Bronesky, Amanda (Box 18)
      Program included, Date from binder, Film form included
    - SQ Senior Prom Show/ People Cutting Class, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00014; Taylor, Devon (Box 18)
    - Jackson Jills, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00015; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - Tub of Joy/ Into the Woods, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00016; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Rabbi Summit Rocks Out in Metcalf, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00017; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Craft's Sale, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00018; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Into the Woods Rehearsals, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00019; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - And Then They Came For Me, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00020; Bedoya, Andrea (Box 18)
    - Applied Musical Recital, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00021; Boudreau, Laura (Box 18)
    - Turbo, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00022; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - Turbo, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00023; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - YGS Band, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00024; Taylor, Devon (Box 18)
    - Stop Kiss, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00025; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - Fall Fest 2001, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00026; Rebek, Eva (Box 18)
    - Fall Fest 2001, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00027; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Playboy of the Western World, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00028; Wittels, Will (Box 18)
    - Sarah Jessica Parker - Hasty Pudding Award, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00029; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Puppets, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00030; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Steven Kunken speaks to 3 P's, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00031; Taylor, Devon (Box 18)
    - Tufts ID; Next Stage Theater Co., 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00032; Bedoya, Andrea (Box 18)
    - Songstreet Folk Fest, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00033; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Supershow, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00034; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Supershow, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00035; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Filler!!, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00036; Carre, Raynald A. (Box 18)
    - Filler!!, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00037; Carre, Raynald A. (Box 18)
    - Dance Class, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00038 (Box 18)
    - Someday Cafe; Starbucks; Deisel Cafe, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00039; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Spirit of Color Rehearsal, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00040; Turgeon, Evan (Box 18)
    - How I Learned to Drive, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00041; Turgeon, Evan (Box 18)
    - Bangra Dance Group; Laundry Room stuff, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00042; Ko, Jen (Box 18)
    - Pep Band Practice, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00043; Villar, Lucy (Box 18)
    - Aidekman Arts Gallery, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00044; Chan, Melissa (Box 18)
    - Josh Sestel Lecture, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00045; Carre, Raynold (Box 18)
    - Soc Practice, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00046; Chan, Marie (Box 18)
    - Oxfam 10-12, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00047; Chan, Melissa (Box 18)
    - A Capella Performances at Tisch Rooftop, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00048; Carre, Raynold (Box 18)
    - Arts Concert, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00049; Ko, Jen (Box 18)
    - Union Square, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00050; Ko, Jen (Box 18)
    - Romeo and Juliet Rehearsal (Act 3), 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00051; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 18)
    - Penn Masala, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00052; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Hubba Hubba Sex Shop, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00053; Rubin, Tim (Box 18)
    - Nexus Theater Center, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00054; Bedoya, Andrea (Box 18)
    - The Arts Haus, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00055; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 18)
    - Cafe de Crepe, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00056; Raha, Joya; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Torn Ticket II, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00057; Justin (Box 18)
    - Pluto; Oxfam, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00058; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Somerville Theater and Crafts Center, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00059; Chan, Melissa (Box 18)
    - Brown and Brew Patio, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00060; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Copley - Prudential, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00061; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Billy Joel, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00062; Lee, Marie (Box 18)
    - Billy Joel, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00063; Golub, Justin (Box 18)
    - Random Pictures around campus, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00064; Hayden, Elizabeth (Box 18)
    - Fall Comedy Show, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00065; Trevor (Box 18)
    - Fall Comedy Show, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00066; Trevor (Box 18)
    - Arts, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00067; Silberberg, Jacob (Box 18)
    - Arts, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00068; Silberberg, Jacob (Box 18)
    - Random shots, 2001; UA176.002.018.00004.00069 (Box 18)
    - Toad the Wet Sprocket, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00070; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Toad the Wet Sprocket, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00071; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
    - Daniel Aaronson; Jordan Kolasinski, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00072; Steinvurzel, David (Box 18)
    - Purnim, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00073; Taylor, Devon (Box 18)
    - Stellar, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.018.00004.00074; Berkowitz, Amy (Box 18)
  - Features, Fall and Spring, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.019.00001
    - Campus Media, 2001; UA176.002.019.00001.00001; Bronesky (Box 19)
      Film form included with negative
    - Homemade Ice Cream; Random shots, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00002 (Box 19)
    - Sabor Restaurant, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00003; Wittels (Box 19)
      Date from binder, Film form included with negative
    - Assassins, 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00004; Wittels (Box 19)
    - Islamic Center; Capen House (African Center), 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00005; Yaaziz, Nik (Box 19)
    - El Salvador Presentation, 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00006; Brandt, Mellisa (Box 19)
      Note with negative
    - Dean Cuttino, 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00007; Hayden, Elizabeth (Box 19)
    - Ginn Library, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00008; Takahashi, Akiko (Box 19)
    - Father O'Leary - Chairman of Institutional Review Board, 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00009; Boudreau, Laura (Box 19)
    - Dean Leila Fawaz - Endowed Chair of Middle Eastern Studies, 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00010; Boudreau, Laura (Box 19)
    - Headshots of Raja Taunk, 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00011; Boudreau, Laura (Box 19)
    - Kindness Week, 2001 -- 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00012; Wittels, Will (Box 19)
    - Tufts Univ. Center for Children Community of Scholars Luncheon, 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00013; Meisel, Alison (Box 19)
    - Bilingual Students, 2002; UA176.002.019.00001.00014; Bedoya, Andrea (Box 19)